(Sheldon:)from Buckland.
(Sheldon:)And I roll...
(Sheldon:)a five and a three.
(Bernadette:)Okay.
(Leonard:)And to defend, I roll...
(Leonard:)two sixes. I win.
(Sheldon:)Boy, double-sixes again.
(Leonard:)You know...
if I hadn't seen it
(Sheldon:)with my own eyes,
I wouldn't believe it.
(Sheldon:)I wonder how long
we're gonna be stuck here.
(Leonard:)I don't know, but the girls
do a lot for us.
(Leonard:)It's the least we can do.
(Sheldon:)Oh, that's true.
I suppose it's only fair
(Sheldon:)we make compromises.
(Leonard:)Look at you,
being all mature.
(Sheldon:)I don't know why
you're so surprised.
(Sheldon:)If there's one thing I know
about after living with you
(Sheldon:)for so many years,
it's how to compromise.
I-I'm sorry?
(Leonard:)You make compromises for me?
(Sheldon:)All the time.
(Leonard:)On Earth?